- The food was delicious, sir.
- Thank you, sir.
Mom, please wake Jeeva up.
- He's getting late for school.
- Oh, so you're Tamilians?
Where are you from? Chennai?
We're not from Chennai.
A town near Madurai.
You wouldn't know.
Oh, you're from Madurai!
Sir, isn't this one of Madurai's
most popular hotel chains?
This is not the same.
That's my name.
I just added "Hotel" to my name.
Oh, now I get it.
You dropped the "H" from "Hotel."
Sir, is this your family?
Yes.
This is my wife.
Jeeva, you're getting late.
Hurry up and get ready.
- Ma'am, do you have chutney?
- I'll get it.
This is my brother-in-law.
As in your wife's brother?
Yeah.
This is my mother-in-law.
Your son is very cute.
What's his name?
Jeeva.
But your son
did not take after his mother.
He takes after you.
Instead of minding your own business
and having breakfast,
why would you cause chaos
early in the morning?
Sir, why would you make such a remark?
We already have too many problems
in the family.
- Please leave, Sir.
- Sorry, Sir!
Okay, Sir, see you!
Bro! My dear, Bro!
Even the victorious have fallen
Many who failed still prevailed
Bro! My dear, Bro!
Jeeva, whom do you like the most?
Mom or Dad?
I like Mom!
But I like my Dad more than her.
Please don't rat me out to my Mom.
Because Mom and Dad are having problems.
I get it!
Beyond winning and losing
Lies a single truth
- Bye, Grandma.
- Bye.
- Dad!
- Yeah!
Yesterday in school,
they conducted a running race.
- Yeah?
- My friend Prakash won the race.
The entire school cheered for him.
Is that so? That's great!
When will I be able to participate
in a running race, Dad?
Next year, my dear.
Yay! Jolly!
What Bro? Why Bro?
That's how life rolls, Bro
Me Bro, You Bro, Everybody Bro!
My dear, Bro!
Jeeva, do well, okay!
All the best!
- Bye!
- Bye, Dad!
Upon life's stage, all are actors
And must perform
My dear, Bro!
The creator of the stage
Reigns in imagination
At his command, all must yield
My dear, Bro!
Life is theater
Understand the script
Be perceptive,
And no role is beyond you
Bro! My dear, Bro!
What Bro? Why Bro?
That's how life rolls, Bro
Me Bro, You Bro, Everybody Bro!
My dear, Bro!
Brother, could you look after my shop?
- I'll be back soon.
- Sure, make it fast.
I reckon your father is late today, too.
When he comes to get me, neither
am I going to talk to him nor go home.
Bro! My dear, Bro!
Hello, is it happening?
Hey, I'm not coming. You carry on.
Hello, Sir. Late as usual.
Someone already took away Jeeva.
Who took him away?
- I just arrived.
- Yes, Sir. But you're late.
So, his uncle came to pick him up.
Which Uncle?
How are you related to the boy?
- I'm his father.
- Mother.
- Grandma.
- Uncle.
- You guys are Tamil, are you?
- Yes, Sir!
How could you be so irresponsible?
Why would you arrive late
to pick up your son each day?
Sorry, Sir!
It's my fault I was late.
Fine, don't be afraid.
We'll check the CCTV camera
and find out who took him.
Sir,
that's Jeeva.
Sir, please fast forward.
Sir, you could spot his face in this clip.
He took away your son.
- How dare you lie?
- Where is the money?
- How dare you con people?
- Would you repeat it?
- Confess, damn it!
- I ought to!
- How dare you mess in our locality?
- I'll skin you if you don't 'fess up.
- I won't spare you!
- Don't you dare attempt this again.
I ought to!
- Open your mouth, and confess!
- Oh no!
- I said, confess!
- More beatings will make him talk.
Bloody arrogant people.
Who are these people?
This couple conned people
out of their money in Laxmi Nagar.
- They got caught.
- Why did you guys get caught?
What happened to you guys?
Why do you have casts on?
Last night I slipped and fell
in the bathroom.
- That's why I'm in a cast.
- What happened to you?
Did you both go to the bathroom together?
COUPLE ARRESTED FOR FRAUD
IN MANGALAPURAM, CHENNAI!
SUDHA HOUSE
How dare you reject my call?
I'll teach you a lesson
when I get a hold of you.
Chutti Anna, one Dosa, quick.
Saravana, the cook, has stepped out.
Could you please wait for 15 minutes?
5 minutes?
Okay, sir.
- Chutti Anna!
- Hi, Sadha.
Please check how much I owe you.
1,240 rupees.
- Here's 1,000. I'll pay the balance later.
- Sure!
How much?
- Chutti Anna!
- Tell me.
I have a plan called Quick Money.
Would you like to invest in it?
What is Quick Money?
Aren't you aware of it?
You start making a profit
the instant you invest in it.
- That's Quick Money.
- Instant profit?
- How does it work?
- Making a quick buck won't last.
Pay the bill and be on your way.
Please leave, Sir.
Hey, what does the board say?
It says, "Do not discuss politics and
business here with the customers."
Chutti Anna!
It says not to discuss with the customers.
- Yes!
- But I'm speaking to the owner.
- Hi!
- Hello!
- Couldn't find a customer yet?
- No luck!
At present, everyone has become smart.
So, it's tough.
Forget about me.
Did you settle your issues?
Not yet. Problems still exist.
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine.
It should be fine.
Or I should make it fine.
Why are you troubling yourself?
Please give me your card.
I'll pay and bring it back to your house.
- Is the AC voltage in summer low?
- Yes, sir!
- But it works well in the rainy season.
- Yes, sir.
It doesn't work well when needed.
When we don't need it,
it works well.
- Do you live on Lal Bahadur Street?
- Yes, sir.
I, too, live on the same street.
I am facing the same issue at home.
Don't worry. We'll fix it.
Have faith.
Venkatachalam!
Good morning, Sir.
Hey, don't push me around.
Step aside.
Don't step on my toes.
I ought to!
Hey! Hey! Move, woman!
Hey, it's the ladies' queue.
Move to the other queue.
My question exactly.
What are you doing in the ladies' queue?
Early drinker, you are.
Don't piss me off.
I'll close the counter.
- Hey, there's an emergency at home.
- I said to switch the queue.
- Hi, sir. Good morning.
- Hi, Saravana.
My wife has an appointment
with the doctor.
Also, I have to
drop my car off for service.
There's too much of a crowd for billing.
Could you please open your counter?
- Okay, sir.
- Great!
Dear consumers, the other counter is open.
- Switch to it.
- Hey, where are you going?
- I've been waiting for a long time.
- Hey, switch to the other counter.
Are you able to hear the heartbeat?
Only during the 3rd-month scan
would you get a clear picture.
So, don't forget to come for a check-up.
Also, have your food and tablets on time.
During this period, you and the child
should be extra careful.
Okay.
Didn't your husband come with you?
Hello! Who are you, people?
This is my house.
Why are you bringing my stuff outside?
We don't know anything.
The house owner is inside.
Speak to him.
- Hurry up. Take everything outside.
- Hey, who are you?
Finally, you made it.
I've been waiting for a long time.
Hello, first, tell me who you are?
And how did you get in?
Why did you break my lock?
Listen, I'm the owner of this house.
I reckon you rented this house
through Right Choice Properties.
Sir, I leased the house
for three lakh rupees.
What?
You paid three lakh rupees for the lease?
They have swindled your money.
That's a fraudulent company.
They haven't paid me two months' rent yet.
Find out where they are and
file a complaint with the Police.
This is the rental agreement they gave me.
How do you expect me to find them
or get them arrested?
Hey, hurry up and remove things.
- It's getting late.
- Yes.
Stop thinking
and find a way out of this.
It's a fraudulent company.
It's been two months since they closed.
They mentioned to the owners
that they're renting the house...
And swindled money from people
like you and evaded the town.
I grew up in an Orphanage in Kerala.
I am an orphan.
I don't have a stable income.
I thought leasing a house wouldn't mean
paying rent every month...
So, I borrowed money, sold some jewels,
and took out a lease on that house.
But I never expected they would con me.
If I could stay one day here...
I hope it won't be a problem for you.
If it's only for a day,
we have no issues.
Yes, only for a day.
I'm already looking for a place to stay.
I'll leave tomorrow.
Okay. Please make yourself comfortable.
Thank you.
As per the scenario you mentioned,
it sounds very critical, Subramani.
Yes, Doctor. I understand.
I'll speak to them, Doctor.
Sure, Doctor.
Immediately, we must perform
a major surgery on her.
Her health condition is very bad.
This surgery is very critical.
It's impossible to perform.
But we have no choice but to perform.
Sir, I don't understand.
Is it possible
to perform the surgery or not?
Like I mentioned.
Her health condition is very bad.
This surgery is very critical.
It's impossible to perform.
But we have no choice but to perform.
Hey, I don't understand what he's saying.
There's nothing wrong with me.
I am doing well, though.
Let's go home.
Mom, please shut up.
Sir, please explain it clearly.
There's a tumor on her lungs.
It has crossed Stage 3 now.
It's better for her
if we perform the surgery immediately.
It would cost you a lot of money.
Do you have insurance?
How are you placed financially?
We don't have any insurance.
How much would the surgery cost?
Approximately seven to eight lakhs.
The sooner we perform the surgery,
the greater the possibility of curing it.
If you happen to delay it...
I can't guarantee
how long she will be alive.
Please take this
as a very serious warning.
I wish to become a Hero.
My mother used to say this all the time.
So, what if no one produced your film?
We'll produce it ourselves.
Because his father, Rambo Selvaraj,
was a renowned stunt master in cinema.
Moreover, he has done
a lot of good deeds during his time.
My mother said that mentioning
his name is enough to raise funds.
You're asking at the wrong time.
But I'm ready to give my life, though.
I need 8 lakh rupees to save my mother.
I don't have any money.
I'm already in a huge debt.
Jacky, your father allotted this place
under the trust.
You can't sell or mortgage it.
You can use it until it lasts.
Now, when I'm reaching out
to raise funds for Mom's surgery,
no one's helping me out.
In this situation,
producing a film is not possible.
You may use the same story
to direct another Hero.
I wrote this script with you in mind.
I cannot cast another Hero
to make this film.
No matter how long it takes,
I'll wait for you.
First, resolve your issues.
I thought mentioning his name
would help raise funds to make a film.
I told them you're going to die,
yet no one helped me out.
In the name of doing good deeds,
he left us in peril.
Not one soul did he help
is helping us now.
People forget the help
they received recently.
That's the way of life.
Don't torment yourself.
Nothing is wrong with me.
I'm doing well.
When Dad was ill...
he, too, kept saying
nothing was wrong with him,
and in the end, he passed away.
But this time I'm not giving up on you.
If you're gone,
I don't have anyone else.
Hey, why are you crying like a child?
Don't worry. We'll overcome it.
Listen, no one can change fate.
Nothing is wrong with me.
Let it go.
Hey, don't you see I'm rejecting the call?
Why would you keep calling?
Hey, Dad found out about our relationship.
Are you serious?
Who's this boy?
His name is Saravana.
We've been in a relationship
since college.
He's in a secure government job,
and he owns a house.
He's a very good boy.
Are you sure?
Okay!
Latha, let's meet the boy.
My Dad wants to meet you right away.
We'll come to your house shortly.
I'm at the office.
- So what?
- I mean...
Some place near my office...
Why don't we meet at a restaurant?
It's a big deal that
he agreed to meet you.
You'd better get home right away.
For God's sake,
please keep the house clean.
"Keep the house clean."
For God's sake,
please keep the house clean.
So, Saravanan,
what do you do for a living?
I work at the EB office, Uncle.
Actually,
I'm not very interested in this job.
After my mother's demise,
I had to take up a job.
So, I am continuing it.
Actually, I want to become
an entrepreneur, Uncle.
I want to do something Big!
Like, I want to launch my own brand.
I want to launch a new product in
the market and make it successful.
I want to become
a successful businessman like you.
I will make it happen soon.
One minute.
Hey, why the heck
don't you answer my calls?
- Sir!
- Do I look like a moron to you?
Sir, I'm sorry.
Let's step outside and talk.
I won't!
Your house is always locked.
And you don't answer my calls.
You don't pay your EMI, either.
Do you think
I won't reach you at your workplace?
I called you many times.
But you never answered.
I will stand right here and talk.
Sir! Sorry, Sir.
I've been paying EMIs
for the past five years.
The loan principal has not come down,
and the interest is exorbitant.
How would I even manage?
It's not fair.
You should've thought about it before
taking out a loan from a private firm.
Yeah! My mother made a mistake.
I can't pay anymore.
I'll file a complaint with the Police.
You may leave.
Oh, really?
Go ahead and file a complaint.
They can't do anything to me.
If you don't pay your EMI on time,
wait and watch what I do to you!
Dad.
He's a...
...good guy, Dad.
He cheated and lied to you.
I did a background check.
He has borrowed money all over town.
Saravana!
Mom!
Why take a big loan to build this house?
Do you think this is
an ordinary house that anyone can build?
After your father's demise,
we struggled for months
to find a roof over our heads.
There was a time when we didn't
have a permanent address
and paid rent and provided address proof
to live in strangers' houses.
There was a period
when my only desire was
to find a good house to rent.
But I never found one.
Every day after I finish work...
never have I slept peacefully.
I had a wish, though.
Something of our own,
scaling from earth to sky,
I wish to build a house of our own.
Finally, my wish came true.
Saravana, I'm going to sleep
peacefully tonight.
We run and seek
Only to live
Only to exist?
We're all human, aren't we?
Will it change one day?
Will this ever change?
Will these scars ever heal?
Will new paths emerge?
There's something called Ruby Coin.
Everything will be digital money.
It's not the same
as chump change we carry.
In the future,
physical currency won't exist.
- Hey! Hey!
- It's red in color and...
- I have a scheme called Quick Money.
- Quick Money?
I have a scheme called Quick Money.
Did you say, Rukmani?
No, I meant Padmini.
No use in explaining it to you.
I don't understand a word.
Get lost!
Saravana!
Do you know why I like you very much?
It's because of your mother.
The respect you hold for your mother.
I really miss her a lot.
In my service,
I never came across such a woman.
- Is it a photo or a video?
- Video.
Okay, wait.
- Go ahead!
- Record now.
Watch, I'm going to expose you.
Okay? Now, get out!
Don't worry. We'll fix it.
Have faith.
Oh, super!
Sir, I'm here to pay the electricity bill.
Electricity is down.
Come back later.
Is electricity down?
Isn't this the Electricity Board?
Hey, it's not like the EB office
runs on batteries.
Get lost!
Don't you people have any sense?
The system is down.
Move to the next counter.
It's an old card. Get lost!
Do you know my experience in this field?
You weren't even born then.
Get out of here.
Closed!
Udipi coffee!
Amsavalli!
I think I'm getting a migraine.
I'll consult with a doctor and return.
Check what the hell the problem is.
I'm leaving!
Sir, shall I give 10,000 to Saravanan,
as you mentioned over the call?
When did I tell you?
Just because no one lent him money.
He mimicked your voice
and asked for the money.
Oh!
Saravana, is it true?
Sorry, sir.
I didn't hear you.
Come again.
I didn't have another option, sir.
You're not like your mother.
I'm taking back my word.
Just because I like you very much.
Don't do this.
It looks bad, man.
But his voice was better than yours.
Hey, get out of here!
Idiot!
Who grants pain
And claims life in return?
When the spectacle ends,
He seeks another
We run and seek...
No matter how educated you people are,
you're still stupid.
It's easy to take a loan.
But taking another loan is difficult.
If you want to lease a property,
the property owner has to sign it.
Instead of taking a loan
from the Government...
he took a loan from a private firm
because the processing time was less.
In my opinion...
getting cheated is the biggest sin
than cheating.
If we publish this in the media,
it'll backfire on you.
They're private finance firms.
Don't create any problems.
Handle them smoothly in another way.
Buddy, I'd love to take on any work
to earn some extra income.
You want to work for my father?
Just because he was being nice
doesn't mean he's a good man.
He's a cunning man!
Hey, guys!
- Hi, Rithi.
- I got beer, and everything is ready.
We're heading straight to the drive-in
theater to watch the movie Rockstar.
No, I'm not coming.
- You guys carry on.
- Here, take this 25,000 rupees.
Use it to pay this month's EMI.
We'll find a solution soon.
Buddy, no thanks!
You have been helping me every month.
I'm feeling awkward about
taking more money from you.
Will it change one day?
Will this ever change?
Will these scars ever heal?
Will new paths emerge?
Will this phase never end?
Following repeated allegations
of custodial brutality
against Inspector Kalyana Sundaram
of Mangalapuram Police Station...
So, the Human Rights Commission
has ordered an inquiry into him.
Let's hear what the people of Mangalapuram
have to say about him.
In our area, he's famously known
as Pulp-cane Kalyana Sundaram.
He uses a huge cane
to beat the accused to a pulp.
He's beating only the people
who commit crimes.
There's a court to pass a verdict.
Who gave him the right to beat up people?
Only after he got posted here.
This is when this area is crime-free.
Even if we gather in groups to chatter,
he beats us to a pulp.
It's because of Kalyana Sundaram, Sir,
my son reformed and is going to work now.
I packed lunch and am heading to work.
In my opinion,
Kalyana Sundaram is a great man.
I'm sure he was aware.
He knew that he was my brother-in-law,
yet he beat him up.
I'm aware that he's your brother-in-law.
But he's new here.
I'll make sure there are no conflicts
as we move forward.
Let's set aside differences
and compromise.
Saravana!
Here is the money and the EB cards
of my 12 businesses.
Please pay the electricity bill.
There are still 20 days until
the due date. Why the hurry?
On the due date,
most people run out of money.
So, it's best to pay early.
- Please pay the bill.
- Sure, I'll pay it.
- Sir!
- Huh?
My electricity bill is quite high, sir.
Are you married?
Yes, sir.
Ask your wife.
She'll explain it to you.
Sure, sir. I'll check with her.
I like him. Very genuine guy.
- Sir!
- Yeah.
Sir, I'm not married.
Still, my electricity bill is high.
Holy shit!
Please come closer.
If you don't mind,
shall I arrange a wife for you?
Shameless creatures!
In my experience,
I've never seen such cheap people.
Closed!
EMI payment?
Wait for five minutes, I'll be out.
Sir, here is the money and EB cards
for five houses. Please pay the bill.
Here is the money and the EB cards
of my 12 businesses.
Please pay the electricity bill.
There are still 20 days until
the due date. Why the hurry?
On the due date,
most people run out of money.
So, it's best to pay early.
Please pay the bill.
Sir, please wait for five minutes.
I'll be back.
This is one month's EMI.
Please adjust and get me an extension.
I'll clear everything then.
If you don't pay your EMI in a day,
wait and watch what I do to you.
Ask him to pay the EMIs on time.
He has borrowed money all over town.
In my opinion...
getting cheated is the biggest sin
than cheating.
Sir, I saw that your 3BHK house
is up for rent in Mangalapuram.
Yeah, that's my property.
Are you the tenant?
No, sir, I'm Mithra.
I run Standard Property, a property
management company in the same area.
Here's my business card
and the company's address.
Sir, we're managing
100+ premium properties.
And we've been in this field
for more than 10 years.
Fine, okay.
The services that we provide
are to undertake
the client's rental properties
and transfer the rent to the clients
on the said date.
I see you reside in Adyar.
But your property is in Mangalapuram.
It'll be difficult for you to visit often
to check on the property.
As we're situated in the same area,
we'll regularly monitor
and hand you a month-wise report.
Suppose the tenant is behind on rent,
Standard Property
will pay you the rent on time.
Our fee for this service is 10%.
Also, I'll be collecting the same
from the tenant.
You wouldn't have to worry
about your property anymore.
Once you hire
Standard Property Management,
we consider it as our own property.
Sir, I reckon you have quoted 10,000
rupees as the rent for your property.
But as per the market rate,
you can quote up to 15,000 rupees as rent.
To be honest, your previous tenant
has cheated you all this time.
Here's your agreement.
Thank you, Sir.
Sir, here's your copy.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you, Sir.
One minute.
Since 1998, means...
Is your main branch located in Chennai?
No, Sir, our main branch
is located in Trichy.
Trichy!
Okay!
Okay? Okay!
2,000.
Credited... 4,000!
8,000.
Mom!
I posted on Facebook
through the Rambo Trust
to raise funds for your treatment.
Many people have transferred money
to that account online.
Until now, I have received 24,000 rupees.
Are you serious?
Is it from the Rambo Trust?
Yes, it is from the trust.
Mom, as we speak,
5,000 has been credited.
I think we'll be able to raise the funds
needed for your surgery.
Listen, your father's good deeds
don't have to bear fruit only through him.
It could happen through strangers too.
Go.
It ran out of paper.
Okay.
It's working now.
Here you go.
Brother, your EB cards.
Okay. Have you paid them all?
Thank you so much.
Saravana, I don't see any receipts.
You see, the printer
at the office broke down.
We couldn't issue any receipts today.
So, I personally noted
that it had been paid.
No problem, as long as it's been paid.
Thank you so much.
Okay, good night.
Since 1998.
So, where in Chennai
is your main branch located?
The main branch is not in Chennai.
- It's in Madurai.
- Oh, Madurai. Okay.
Ma'am, I'm ready to take
the 2BHK on Pallavan Street.
Here's the five lakh for the lease.
Ma'am, please check once.
- It will be all in.
- Please check once.
- I'm sure it's all in.
- Ma'am, it's 5 lakhs!
Please check once!
There's no harm in checking.
Sir, I've been running this company
for over 10 years.
I have met many clients!
I can easily judge
by a few clients' appearances.
Trust is everything.
Okay, Ma'am.
The minimum lease period
as per the contract is one year.
If you wish to end the contract,
please notify three months in advance.
Okay, Ma'am.
Ma'am, where is this house owner located?
Your house owner is in Canada.
Oh, Canada! Okay, okay, Ma'am.
If you need anything,
reach out to me.
- Sure! Thank you, Ma'am.
- Okay.
Thank you! Thank you!
Hey, fool!
I just saw the reports you sent in.
It has nothing to do
with the scenario you mentioned.
We would've done many case studies
in college on this matter.
You were always confused.
- You can't even identify a case...
- Shall I pay him?
Mom, shut up.
He's busy talking.
How would you even diagnose?
I can't believe you became a Doctor.
And your parents
have built you a hospital.
I pity your patients!
Hang up the phone, rascal!
Yes, Sir! 100% correct, Sir!
You're right. When we compare it
with the previous report,
since it's not there,
it's no longer a threat.
Thank you, sir.
There's been a huge phenomenal change.
When we checked her current report,
the tumor was from the previous
diagnosis itself.
There's no need for us
to proceed with the surgery.
Hey, didn't I tell you that nothing's
wrong with me, and I'm doing well.
Mom, please shut up.
Doctor, didn't you mention it's a
severe cancer and surgery is critical?
I, too, Googled her condition.
It showed up as severe cancer.
But now you're saying
no need for surgery.
I seriously don't understand.
If you Google it, it'll say
any sickness is a severe condition.
I have been confused many times
Googling for answers.
So, please don't believe Google.
Please follow whatever doctors prescribe.
Does that mean my mother is cured?
Hey, didn't you hear me earlier?
That nothing's wrong with me
and I'm doing well.
Yet you've been asking him questions.
Nothing's wrong with me.
I'm doing well.
She's been cured!
Correct!
I'm prescribing you tablets for 30 days.
If you follow it,
everything will be well.
Sorry, Sir,
we don't need the money right now.
Thank you for donating
in response to the Facebook post.
Okay, Sir!
Mom, let's return the money.
Why should we return the money?
Now you don't need surgery.
Let's return the money
to everyone who donated.
We don't have to return it.
I'll let you know. Wait.
Mom!
Let's wrap this up sooner.
Why do we have to wait?
Don't you still get it,
why we got this money?
Think about it. Why did I fall sick,
and why were we in financial hardship?
And when we got money,
why did I cure myself?
Think about it.
Don't you still understand?
All these years,
you were despising your father.
Only now has he made sense
and made the money available for us.
And you're giving it up easily.
Why did we get this money?
Didn't I mention that
I want to start "Janaki Amma Studios"?
This money is for that.
Mom, have you lost your mind?
These people have been
crediting continuously.
Mom!
Hello, this is Avinash speaking.
I came across a post about raising funds
for Janaki Ma'am's treatment.
Were you able to arrange for the funds?
Not yet, Sir.
Oh, I get it.
I have 10,000 rupees to donate.
I will transfer it to your account.
Please use that for your treatment.
Thank you, Sir.
Janaki Ma'am
is still in critical condition.
Your help is very important to her.
Please spread the message
to as many people as possible.
Okay, I'll share it with everyone.
Thank you, Sir.
Mom,
what are you doing?
Sit down!
Let's resume Rambo Trust.
Why?
So that, like father, we'd make money
to give away as good deeds.
Are you planning to do the same?
First, listen closely to what I am saying.
Let's resume Rambo Trust.
It'll bring in donations.
And we'll help people in need.
Whatever extra we have, let's put it
on rotation and start making our movie.
Mom, it doesn't sound right to me.
Hey, we're not going to con people.
We'll put the money in rotation
and eventually return it.
I don't know.
I'm afraid to do this.
I have a bad feeling
that we'll get caught in a huge problem.
I want to work hard
and become a Hero in cinema.
Your father was honest,
but he didn't do squat.
There's no point in being honest.
You focus on becoming a Hero.
I'll handle the rest.
The people who are donating
won't even know
if we raised enough funds
to meet our requirements.
Until we decide to put a cap on it,
we'll continue to receive funds.
Let it keep coming.
- Remember what Thalaivar quoted?
- What?
To create a few Heroes,
- we can do whatever it takes.
- Mom!
He never quoted anything like it.
Why are you guiding the wrong way?
Buddy, do you know Steve Jobs...
Hey, don't patronize me
as you do with others.
Just explain how the daily profits work.
Fine, I'll let you in on the secret.
Don't tell anyone.
You're aware
that I work for a trading company.
All the rich people in town are
investing in our trading company.
Our job is to invest money in accounts
instructed by our Senior Analyst.
And to withdraw from respective accounts.
Are you personally trading
without the company's knowledge?
- Hey, shut up and mind your business.
- My juniors at work...
are personally profiting
without the company's knowledge.
Hey, you did personal trading
and bought a car so soon.
We're helping strangers make profits.
If not us, who will take care of us?
- Mind your business.
- I helped many strangers make a profit.
Why wouldn't I help myself, Saravana?
I worked at that company for over a year.
After analyzing closely, I'm suggesting
that we can definitely make daily profits.
Generally, people expect
a 10% profit daily.
They're the certified fools.
Our target will be only 2%.
It's very easy to achieve.
You calculate yourself.
You can make 60% profit in a month
without risk.
Sir, there are 20 EB cards.
I'm here to pay the EB bill.
Hey, bring me exact change
for the respective cards.
You know to come early in the morning
to beat the crowd.
Can't you bring exact change?
Take this away and return with change.
Sir, you know, people come early
to pay the bill.
You should be prepared with change.
I'm not a bus conductor
to tender exact change.
Get lost!
Sir, the printer isn't working.
Could you please check?
I'll check!
This printer is always a problem.
Hey, it's an old junk model.
We've placed an order for new printers.
But they'll deliver them
only after they're outdated.
This is our Government.
There's nothing we could do about it.
I think the printer has broken down.
If we wait for a technician,
it'll get delayed.
You do one thing.
After paying all the bills...
...then make a manual entry
of all the receipts.
After the system is ready,
- then you can feed the data.
- Okay, Sir.
We do this often
when there's a technical problem.
- Okay, sir.
- I'll drop my wife off at Prince Jewelry.
- Please manage.
- Okay.
Girls, move to that line.
Join that counter.
Very nice!
You continue your work.
The printer is not working.
Here's the manual receipt.
- Sir.
- Hand it to me.
The printer is not working.
Here's the manual receipt.
- Sir, EB bill.
- Oh, it's you.
Hand it to me.
- What's all this?
- Didn't you ask for change?
Now pay the bill.
Oh, he's the troublemaker.
Sir, suddenly it's printing now.
What shall I do?
It has a mind of its own.
It'll keep going on and off.
Like my wife's mood swings
and anger.
There's a phone number on that door.
Call that technician
and get it fixed.
Okay, Sir.
Bye, Sir.
I'm the King
From this moment on, I rule
I'm about to sound the call
Hey, Satha,
if you get me guaranteed profits...
- I'll invest more money.
- It's easy peasy, Buddy.
If you make this work,
our lives will change for good.
King, King, King
Out here, I'm the King
I'm about to sound the call
Saravana, why is your printer
constantly breaking down?
Why are you staring at me?
Hey, what can he do
if the machine malfunctions?
Don't keep nagging him.
Hey, there are too many people.
Why can't you work efficiently?
Get back to work.
Finish up soon.
I'll handle it. You get lost!
Gopi, sir, asked not to work
if the printer isn't working.
Who's Gopi to bark orders?
Listen to me.
Issue a manual receipt to everyone.
And get back to work, son.
I dropped my wife off
at the Chinese beauty parlor.
I'll drop her off at home and return.
Please handle it, dear.
I feel like quitting the job.
Don't you ever say you're quitting.
I don't want unnecessary problems.
Whenever you say you are quitting,
I get a migraine.
- Please don't say it.
- I think of running away, sir.
Run away?
What's your problem in life? Spill it!
This printer and Gopi, sir,
are my problem.
To hell with Gopi!
You continue to issue manual receipts.
I'm here for you.
I have your back.
My wife...
Today is a new moon day.
I have to take her to the temple
in Mylapore.
Exactly, in four hours,
I'll return to the office.
Please take care of the counters.
- Sure, sir.
- Your printer is working well, right?
Hey! Why does your printer
keep breaking down?
Why do you keep harping
that it's his printer?
If he quits his job,
are you going to sit at the counter?
There's something wrong with that printer.
Why are you so obsessed with the printer?
I've instructed him to issue
manual receipts.
If there's an issue in billing,
we'll be in trouble.
Didn't I tell you
I'm taking his responsibility?
It's me who assured him that
manual receipts won't be an issue.
From today onward,
he's like a son to me.
No matter what the issue is,
I'm responsible for it.
Just because he doesn't talk back,
don't keep nagging him.
Get lost!
Do as you please!
My wife has food poisoning.
Since this morning, she's been vomiting.
I have to take her to Dr. Arun in Guindy.
I applied for two days of sick leave.
- You take care of my counter, too.
- Okay, Sir.
If Gopi gives you a hard time,
please call me.
Saravana, lately the collection is low.
Unlike before, customers don't wish
to pay their bills ahead of the due date.
There's nothing we could do.
Unlike before,
the public has gotten smarter.
No one can fool them.
The public has gotten smarter;
no one can fool them. Isn't it?
Unlike before,
the public has gotten smarter.
No one can fool them.
I'm no villain
I'm no hero
I'm no joker
I stand above them all
I'm the King!
I'm neither "That-God"
- Nor I'm "This-Satan"
- Yes, man.
As you mentioned,
everyone paid on time.
The public has gotten smarter.
No one can fool them.
I'm no gangster
No monster either
I'm here to claim my rightful share
There's no right or wrong anymore
I'm shutting your mouth for good
Buddy, you gave me 2 lakhs.
10 days' profit, 1 lakh.
It's not enough for my situation.
I need more!
Let's collaborate
to do it on a larger scale.
As per your information,
we're getting 60% returns.
I'll start a new company in my area.
We'll find investors.
If we lend it at interest, we get 10%.
We offer 20% guaranteed returns!
You're the inside man.
And I'll handle it outside.
Madam, please check if it's all in there.
I can judge from a client's appearance.
I can sense from your appearance
that it's all in there.
Why don't you count it once?
Your name is Saroja.
My mother's name is also Saroja.
My father's name is also Nagaraj.
Vishnu is my father's name.
If I still go ahead and count the money...
it'll be like I'm suspecting
my own mother.
It'll be like I'm suspecting
my own father.
- I have trust in you, Sir.
- Dad!
You heard her.
Give it back to her.
What happened?
I don't understand.
Sorry, Ma'am,
the bundle was short of 1000 rupees.
Father did ask me to put it back.
But I forgot, Ma'am.
Brother, you must not cheat anyone.
It's a big mistake.
- Understand?
- I'm sorry, Ma'am.
Don't repeat it.
Suddenly, I turned dangerous
I was just one
Now I'm a movement
I was once Civil
But now I turned into a Devil
Sir, here's the 1st month rent
of your property.
Mithra, it's not yet the 1st of the month,
and you already paid the rent.
Sir, like I mentioned
Standard Property Management
will pay sharply before the due date.
Nice!
Love, Drama, Action, Thriller.
- Add this too.
- Comedy?
Fine, adding comedy too.
Love, Drama, Action, Thriller, and Comedy.
- That means our genre is a hit!
- Are you sure?
Only if we rip off from local movies,
they'd call us copycats.
But if I rip off a Korean film...
they'd call us Master of craft.
Okay, Auntie.
Is it possible to meet
that girl in person?
Sure, Karthi!
I'll check with the Doctor right away.
Life may make us prisoners trapped in it.
But breaking out of that prison
or remaining trapped
is in our hands!
Remove hands from the dialogue.
- You should not use your hands.
- Sorry, Director.
They'll never agree to creative ideas.
- Hello, Doctor.
- Yes!
It's regarding patient Pavithra.
A trustee named Karthi
is here to meet her.
- Shall we come over?
- No!
To me, God is everything.
Oh, is it?
My first God...
- ...Money!
- Yes, Doctor.
I forgot about it.
You blinked 5 times.
You must blink only 3 times.
Moreover, you must not blink
during the take.
Hey, read the dialogue.
Roll camera.
- Next take. Okay.
- Next?
They're planning to shift her
to another hospital.
You can pay me, and I'll pass it on.
150 rupees.
- And he cross-checked so many times.
- I don't get it.
I meant 150 RUPEES.
- I want a receipt.
- For 150 rupees?
A good person won't harm anyone.
Even an evil person won't harm anyone.
Both won't harm?
What kind of stupid dialogue is this?
In our film,
there will be no violence.
But I'll be violent.
Move to the next take.
He does not care for anything.
Shit!
There's no modulation or emotion.
Why can't this face project some emotions?
Acting is like a penance.
Why don't you show me how to repent?
He's testing me.
Roll camera. Watch me.
Here, quench your thirst.
In fact, you were good.
Only actors should perform,
not the director.
- Only actors should emote.
- Why the heck did you challenge me?
My assistants are around.
Hey, cut camera!
Hey, why are you recording?
If I pull off a crime without a flaw
People will call it brilliance
Once you become a VIP,
History turns into mystery
It's very tough
even to deliver 10% returns.
How are you able to offer a 20% return?
That's Quick money for you.
We don't invest in Indian companies.
We invest in US companies.
Let me give you
a piece of confidential information.
We have a scheme called Ruby Coin.
It's not the chump change you carry.
In the future,
there will be no physical currency.
It'll all be digital currency.
If you invest in Ruby Coin...
in the next year,
you'll be the richest person in this area.
For now, I'll invest three lakhs.
First, I'll invest one lakh.
You return 20% interest.
Later, I'll decide.
Stacks of money
Doesn't that say enough?
Indeed, it's con-money
Whatever I touch becomes a hit
Buddy, if we keep the money in rotation
- for sure we'll become rich in a year.
- You're right, Satha.
I hope we won't get caught.
We're rotating the public money from EB
and pay it back before the due date.
Similarly, we take money
from the customers as an investment
and invest that money
in your trading company.
As you guarantee a 60% profit as return
is how I can guarantee
the customers 20% profit as return.
We won't get caught
if we keep up this technique.
Because we're not conning people.
Yeah, we're not conning people.
- But they're getting conned by us.
- I ought to!
Get lost!
No use in telling you.
Let unrest rise in every heart...
Nurture it, and it becomes a storm
One bite of that rock-solid roti
Grandpa's dentures turned red quickly
Let the whole city rise and applaud
Tighten the cage...
Watch me tear it apart
Even Harry Potter gets knocked out
In one shot
If needed,
I unleash Power Rangers Ninja Storm
Uncle, I'm still a debtor.
Not the borrowing one.
But the lender.
I'm the Lord
I run things now
Every empire starts small
When it comes to money...
I'm the Boss
Let God Himself try to stop me
Gotta live larger than life
We should become the talk of the town
On the penthouse terrace
Buddy... I'll descend on the helipad
I'm the King
From this moment on, I rule
I'm about to sound the call
King, King, King...
How come an Audi car?
- You see...
- Stop! Engagement ring. I got it.
It's a gift from your father-in-law.
Am I right?
- Yes.
- I don't mind how the girl is.
But I want a father-in-law
like Saravanan's father-in-law.
Such a humble person.
Lucky boy.
I did tell you, people.
But no one believed me.
- Look over there.
- You're right, Sir.
Hey! Where are you looking?
Look at the Rolex watch he's wearing.
Saravanan's father-in-law gifted him.
You're settled for life
'cause of your father-in-law
I don't know if one exists for me.
I'm no villain
I'm no hero
I'm investing 53 lakhs.
I'm investing 40 lakhs.
I'm investing 20 lakhs.
It's hard-earned money, Son.
Nor I'm "This-Satan"
I'm not Just-Human either
- Thank you.
- I'm the King who reigns supreme
Hey, it's the Old Korean Boy.
Directors have already
ripped off this story part by part.
Hey!
You said if you rip off from Korean movies
people call us Master of the craft.
Can't you even copy properly?
It's a rip-off!
Still, it will work with the audience.
- Thank you, Sir.
- Okay, Sir.
Pose well.
Another pose.
Change pose.
Oh, Old Boy?
Have you watched it already?
It's not the same movie.
- Oh!
- You can't even copy a poster.
- Hey!
- Stop right there.
- Don't do it.
- Don't!
- Hey, Kumar, stop right there.
Hello!
- Me?
- Yes, you!
- Tell me!
- How can you not have AC or car parking?
- How do you expect me to dine here?
- Don't dine here!
Dude!
That's why I suggested
going to Cafe Coffee Day.
But you never listened.
Hello! This table is very lucky for us.
We're planning to invest in this table.
Tell me how many lakhs you need.
I'll write you a single check.
Table and four chairs.
It's only 3,000 rupees.
Pay and carry it over your head.
Or else drag it out of here.
- Shit!
- Why would you?
Ma'am, this month's toll collection
is 10.25 crore rupees.
Okay, Krishna.
- You may leave.
- Thank you, Ma'am.
After marriage, Dad is planning
to give this toll as a gift to you.
King, King, King
Out here, I'm the King
- I'm about to sound the call
- Rithi...
...is pregnant, buddy.
Out here, I'm the King
King, King, King
I'm about to sound the call
Brother, quickly finish the work.
Buddy!
You had requested to borrow
10 crores from Ganesh Sait.
Yes!
Shall I arrange that money for you?
I need 10 crores as investment.
You say Rithi is pregnant.
How are you going to manage?
All these years,
I looked after my father's business.
I know how to start my own business.
How are you going to raise
10 crore in investment?
Hey, it's a huge risk.
You're already in a lot of trouble.
How would you arrange the money for me?
Let it go, Buddy. I'll handle it.
Trust me. I know an investor.
I'll say it's for me
and pass on the funds to you.
If you make a profit,
I'll be relieved of my problems, too.
That's a good point.
It makes sense, though.
But think about it.
If it's not an issue, arrange the money.
Okay?
Why did you ask me to withdraw
all the money from the bank so urgently?
Hey, Satha, I came across a great deal.
If we invest 10 crores in two days,
they'll return 15 crores.
Think about it.
We'll make a profit in two days
that would take us a year to earn.
5 crores in profit in two days.
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
A huge consignment is arriving
at the harbor.
It's enough
if we safely take it outside the harbor.
We'll make 20 crores.
But I need 10 crores for expenses.
I only need 5 crores.
But if we invest 10 crores
Ganesh Sait said he will return
15 crores in two days.
Once I close this deal,
she and I will leave for Kolkata.
Is the client trustworthy?
Like you're my school friend,
he's my college friend.
But I'm short of cash.
I have 50 lakhs in savings.
Shall I go home and bring it?
Hey, super! You bring it.
I, too, shall go to the EB office
and bring some money.
Didn't you complain that your printer
keeps breaking down?
- It's working fine.
- Sir, I did tell you.
It goes on and off.
Oh! Okay, you carry on.
Hey, get in line.
Fall in line. Come on, quick.
Stop chattering and stay quiet.
Sir, I can handle this crowd.
Why trouble yourself?
How come you became so helpful?
Gangadhar went on medical leave
and requested to cover for him.
So, I am here.
Saravana, thanks for getting me tickets
for Enthiran FDFS.
I told Gopi that I'm sick.
You maintain the same.
Hey, why did you ask him
to help with your counter?
I asked him to cover for me
so you won't be alone at the counter.
I'm going to watch my Hero's film.
I'm very excited. Let me go!
Hello? Hello?
Dear audience! Did you celebrate
Enthiran's carnival in your town?
Courier your video to us,
recorded on a DVD.
We will air your video
in the coming weeks.
Hello, and Vanakkam,
this is Adam speaking.
I'm happy to meet you all
in the Superstar special show.
Today, Enthiran has been released,
and Superstar's fans are celebrating
in theaters worldwide.
Let's see who's the first lucky caller
on this show.
- Hello!
- Hello...
Am I speaking to VJ Adams?
Yeah, tell me.
I'm calling from Rajini sir's residence.
Sir would like to speak to you.
One minute.
I'll pass the phone to him.
Please give him the phone.
Good morning, Adams.
This is Rajinikanth speaking.
Sir, very good morning, sir.
Dear, how are you?
I'm a big fan of your show.
Good job!
Fantastic! Hats off! Hats off!
Sir! Sir! I'm doing extremely well.
Sir, I'm at a loss for words.
Sir, I'm a big fan of yours.
I heard, Adams.
Thank you. Thank you.
Sir, I have come to your doorstep
on each of your birthdays.
Oh, no, what's this, dear?
Why didn't you call me?
Sir, how could I?
I don't have your number.
Come on, Adams.
It's, after all, a number.
Here, note it down.
90941133...
Sir, you gave your number
over live telecast.
Are you serious, Adams?
Isn't this your personal number?
Sir, you called in to a live show.
What's all this, dear?
Remove the number during the edit.
Sir, it's already live.
How could this happen?
Please request everyone not to call me.
Alaikum Salaam. God bless you.
Sir!
To all the audiences watching the show.
For God's sake,
don't call and trouble him.
And in the history of Television,
this is the only show where
Rajini sir called in.
And I'm the only host who spoke to him,
and here's a song for you.
I'm going to speak to him.
Here you go, Sir!
- Hello?
- Thalaiva! My God!
This is Erode Hari speaking.
I'm your ardent fan.
I installed a 60-foot cut-out for you.
Wrong number, Sir.
-Thalaiva, you looked like a real Robot!
- I'm not a robot, but a human.
Are you going to work
or just speak over the phone?
Hey, please wait!
I worship you like a God.
Hey, I'm not a God!
Hand me your card!
Hey!
Who the hell are you?
How long should I wait?
You're always on the phone.
Hey, please stay silent.
I'm your devotee!
Devotee? Whose devotee?
I'm warning you. Hey!
Hey, what the hell?
Next movie update?
Who are you?
Hey!
Hang up!
Are you going to take our payments,
or shall I file a complaint against you?
Hey, shut up!
Saravana, can you manage?
Okay, Sir.
Everyone, shift to that queue.
Buddy, over here.
Look, there are 10 crores in it.
Fine, inform the investor
that we'll return it in 2 days.
Okay, Buddy.
I'm borrowing from you
for the first time.
- Bye, Buddy!
- Bye.
Saravana, did you watch the news?
Someone has murdered Sabari.
Popular businessman
Bhaskar's son Sabari,
during an illegal business deal,
was shot dead in a crossfire
between two gangs.
A special squad has been assigned
to nab the killers,
and an investigation is underway.
It's better if you leave from here.
Get out!
- He was my only son.
- I told you not to yell and leave.
Sabari...
Oh, God, no!
- Saravana, Sabari...
- Sit down.
- Please look at me, Son.
Sabari!
Who's going to call me mother anymore?
Please look at me.
You never paid heed to me.
And now I'm here without a son.
Hey, Murthy, find out who shot him.
- Oh, no!
- No one should be spared alive.
There's 25,000 in it.
Use this to pay this month's EMI.
We'll handle the rest later.
I'm borrowing from you
for the first time.
Think about it. If you don't have
any problem, make the arrangement.
Didn't you request help through
Rambo Trust for treatment 4 months ago?
No, Brother.
My treatment was over 2 years ago.
Two years, you say?
Do you know the value of a Trust?
It's a grave sin to break one's trust.
A person came home claiming
he was the owner of the house.
In 10 days, if you don't return
the money to the respective people,
I'll file a complaint with the police.
Many fraudsters are roaming around
claiming they're homeowners.
Don't trust anyone.
Mithra, it's the 10th of the month.
You haven't paid the rent.
There's an issue with the bank.
You'll get your rent in 5 days.
I will handle it.
It's because of you we're in this pickle.
Chutti Anna,
did you happen to see Saravana?
I've been trying for 20 days
his phone is not reachable.
You haven't paid rent in a while.
We signed everything at Standard Property.
Standard Property is a scam, Sir.
She's a fraud, and so is her company.
- I'll take you to the Police station.
- File a complaint, damn it!
- Who are you?
- I'm the house owner.
Please repeat what you said.
I'm the house owner.
How many times should I repeat?
I ought to!
How many will claim the same?
Why are you beating me up?
How many of you are out there?
- Why are you beating me?
- I will beat you!
Jacky and Janaki,
in the name of Rambo Trust,
conned many and swindled money.
A pregnant woman, Mithra,
in the pretense of leasing out a house,
has scammed many people.
We are all educated, yet we got conned.
I don't know who truly is my house owner.
How can I claim
I did not pay the EB bill?
Listen, I paid my bill.
I will file a complaint.
- This is fraud.
- Who is a fraud?
- I have been paying regularly.
- You or me?
Manual receipt.
Please leave now
and come back in the evening.
Saravana is a good boy.
Saravana... I don't think so.
What?
Why would they shut down power?
All are manual receipts.
I'll call you. Please sit down.
- Hey, where's the EB money?
- Dad!
- You better confess.
- Dad, I did not take it.
Saravana...
I'll call you all one by one.
They left the fuse right here.
Hey, Saravana!
- Operator!
- Hey, Operator!
Why would they
switch off the power in a theater?
It's a crucial scene.
And they chose to cut the power.
I'm worked up!
You're right!
Hey, Gangadhara, I warned you.
The printer kept getting busted,
and I knew something fishy was going on.
You never listened!
You were coddling him.
He kept issuing manual receipts
and screwed us over.
You kept yelling
that you'll take responsibility.
Stop it!
I'm already very pissed off.
Sir, sir, sir, don't do it.
Hey, don't go inside!
Hey! Hey! Hey, step aside.
Do you know who he is?
- First, tell me, who are you?
- Do you not know me?
I'm the one who answers the phone
when you call the EB office.
- Oh, it's you!
- Yeah!
Oh, why are you beating me up?
How dare you not answer our calls?
Sir, they're carrying me.
- Wait, wait!
- Hey, carry and throw him away.
- They whacked me.
- I saw.
It's all because of you.
Sir, they're flying me in the air
like a kite.
- Please save me, Sir.
- Oh, no!
I'm afraid of heights.
Why are they carrying him like Superman?
They're carrying me
like the ants carrying their food.
Hey, put him down, people.
Please calm down.
You cut off our electricity
and are living in luxury here.
Sir, I can't take it anymore.
Bloody sinners. Please spare me.
In my experience,
I've never witnessed such a sequence.
It's very pathetic!
It has now come to light
that an EB official collected
electricity bill payments from the public,
issued fake receipts,
and swindled crores of rupees.
Why is there no electricity
at the station?
What's with the commotion?
Tell me, where you have hidden the money?
NAME - JANAKI
AGE - 55
NAME - JACKIE
AGE - 25
NAME - MITHRA
AGE - 23
NAME - SARAVANA
AGE - 25
Sir, his face is visible in this clip.
He took away your son.
Kalyana Sundaram!
Mangalapuram witnessed a series
of different scams in a single day.
You used donations as a pretext
to scam countless people.
Don't you feel ashamed?
Jacky and Janaki,
using the Rambo Trust as a front,
conned people out of their money.
Where have you stashed the money?
A pregnant woman Mithra,
in the pretense of leasing out a house,
has scammed many people.
Where have you stashed the money?
Tell me!
An EB officer, Saravanan,
pocketed electricity bill payments
by issuing fake receipts,
swindling crores.
Also, he started something
called Quick Money.
He swindled more
from the people for Mangalapuram.
Has come to the authorities' notice.
"Saravana has been arrested
by the police."
Madam, you can't do this
inside the Police station.
Sir, please take her away.
You bloody fraud!
I can't believe
I was in love with you all these years.
Sorry, Aishu.
Despite you being in debt, I was ready
to get my daughter married to you.
I never imagined you were a con artist.
It's a good thing we learned your
true nature before the wedding.
Hey! We've seen plenty of people
put on an act in front of the police.
Don't hide the truth and confess.
That would be good for you.
- Where did you stash the money?
- I am...
...telling the truth, Sir.
The money is with Sabari.
You better confess where you stashed it
or who's holding the money?
I swear I gave it to Saravana.
Saravanan?
Why is everyone pointing at Saravanan?
Are you trying to blame him and escape?
Sir, I swear
I gave the money to Saravana!
Every one of you is pointing at Saravanan.
You'd better confess where you stashed
the money you looted from the Trust.
Confess, damn it!
Tell him!
Speak up!
Sir, in the next cell,
there is Saravanan.
I gave him the money.
Hey!
Sir, I feel sorry for this old woman.
But this man looks like a criminal.
You look like my daughter,
who went missing when she was a child.
I'm your son, standing right beside you,
yet you still choose to lie.
Am I not your only son?
Are you guys putting up a family drama?
- Sir...
- You better confess!
Sir, I swear, we gave it to Saravanan...
Wait! I'm giving you one last chance.
Mocking me?
Sir, sir, sir, sir, sir! Oh, no!
You guys are pointing fingers
at each other.
You people are lying one after the other.
Confess now and tell us
where you've hidden the cash.
Didn't I give it to you?
Tell him.
I gave the money to you.
Saravana, we gave you the money.
Please give up the location.
I swear
I gave all the money to my friend.
But now he's dead.
For no reason, don't get me beaten up.
Don't embarrass me in front of women.
Please tell the truth.
Sir, we gave him the money.
- He has the money.
- Sir, I gave him the money.
Hey, I'm certain now.
They're putting up a major act.
But one thing they've rehearsed well.
Pitch-perfect performances.
Yes, Sir.
Yes!
Encounter?
Did he mention an encounter?
I'll make the arrangements.
Hey, show me your hands.
Show me your bloody hands!
- Sir, let's escape.
- Hey, let go of me!
Hey!
- Hey, cuff him!
- Let go of me!
- Bloody man.
- Mom, let's go.
Let's go!
Hey, where are the accused?
Why did you let them escape?
Here's the thing.
This vehicle is headed to Karnataka.
I'll get dropped here.
Wherever you people wish to go,
please go safely.
Safely?
Boss, you return my money
and go wherever you wish.
Return my money,
and I'll be on my way.
Don't you guys believe anything I said?
I swear I don't have the money.
I gave the money to my friend,
and now he's dead.
- Hey!
- One day...
I'm a con artist myself,
and you're trying to con me.
You're trying to get rid of us
and swindle all the money.
Hey, I won't let it happen!
- You better return my 42 lakhs--
- Hey, fool!
It's 53 lakhs.
Yeah, if you don't return my 53 lakhs...
I won't spare you.
Pay up, damn it!
Right! Return my 82 lakhs,
and go wherever you wish.
82 lakhs?
You have invested more than we have.
You people still do not
understand the situation.
Like you, many people have
entrusted me with their money.
I have no idea
how I am going to return it.
But I swear I will return it.
Right now, I don't have the money.
I understand, Son.
I understand your problem.
What do you understand?
Hey, he's promising to return the money.
How long would it take
for you to return it?
Mom, I'm extremely pissed!
Right from the beginning,
I was against it.
But you dragged me into this.
Because of him,
I got thrashed in the Police station.
Right now, we're running from the law.
And you're supporting him.
Shut up!
Hey, I want my money back.
If I intended to cheat you all...
why would I break you all
out of the prison?
Hey, you're the reason
the Police caught us?
But you're speaking like a saint.
Listen, I don't care about them.
I want my money.
Without the money, I won't leave.
Bloody, you can't move from here
until you return my money.
- I'll kill you!
- Sir, in Tamil cinema...
you're going to be a popular Hero.
How could you behave like this?
Looking at your actions,
I won't even become a junior artist.
Hey, return my money.
- Return my money!
- Sir! Sir!
Sir, let go of me.
The gang of fraudsters
escaped from police custody.
The police are looking for them.
Kalyana Sundaram.
Sir!
The Principal has summoned you.
I'm coming.
Let's go immediately
and file a complaint with the Police.
Meanwhile, I'll go and meet the Principal.
Police!
Kalyana Sundaram figured out
where we were hiding.
That's why he kidnapped Jeeva.
Why did he even kidnap Jeeva?
He's a child.
He did not do anything.
He's innocent.
Only if he kidnaps the child
could he get to us.
I'm well aware
of Kalyana Sundaram's traits.
If he gets to us, he'll kill us for sure.
Wait, let's see what Saravanan has to say.
Once he's here, we'll discuss it.
What do you think he's going to say?
If you bring him up again,
I'll get pissed.
He's the reason
we've been staying hidden for years.
Still, you think he's going to fix it.
He wouldn't have left
if it were his child.
Tell me!
He must have already fled town.
He's not coming back!
Yet you're supporting him--
I did not run away.
I came to inform you all before leaving.
I'm going to Mangalapuram.
I know you people are angry with me.
I'm the root cause of all the problems.
I will fix it!
Are you all wondering if I really mean it?
Maybe...
I'm not
Jeeva's biological father.
However, according to Jeeva...
I'm his father!
He must be anticipating...
that I'll come and save him.
You, people, don't have to come with me.
I'm leaving.
Saravana!
I'm coming with you too.
My love, are you the song of my life?
My whole world lives in you
Mithra, what are you waiting for?
Let's go!
My sky, my moon
You are the meaning of my life
Everywhere I look,
I see your face,
For you are my precious one
My love, are you the song of my life?
My whole world lives in you
Dad...
...Da!
Shall I sing to you as a father would?
For I sowed you within my very life,
My son
Listening to countless stories
In your baby babble...
Together in your playful mischief,
Your laughter turned our home
Into a song
Climb onto my shoulders, my son,
So that one day you may rise
Beyond me
Not for you to follow
In my footsteps forever,
But for you to go farther and faster
Than I ever did
Yet my love for you
Shall remain unchanged
May my affection never change
For I planted you
Within my very life,
my son
My love, are you the song of my life?
- My whole world lives in you
- Quickly make me a dosa, Mom.
- Grandma?
- Eat, my dear!
Shall I sing to you as a father would?
My precious life,
Both my eyes search for you
My dear son,
Let me sing a lullaby
My precious life,
Both my eyes search for you
Let me sing a lullaby
Sir, we made a mistake by escaping
from your police station.
But they have nothing to do
with this matter.
I'm the root cause of it.
I will surrender myself to the Police.
Oh!
So you people are under the
impression that you escaped from me?
I let you all escape.
Let them escape.
I'm not in the service anymore.
I'm a retired officer now.
According to the people of Mangalapuram,
I'm an honest inspector.
I upheld that name and retired
from the service.
Please wait.
Please wait, Madam.
What is your problem, people?
We were upset,
so we came to bid you goodbye.
I'm not getting transferred.
I'm just retiring.
I'm happy!
But those fools are unaware
of the other side of me.
I'm the person who'd do anything
for the right price.
Bribery, forgery, kidnapping,
fake encounters,
drug supply, I've done it all.
The only motive is money.
After retirement, until I die,
I wish to live rich.
After my retirement,
I had a lot of money.
Initially, I started small-time betting.
I won!
After that,
I got the desire to keep winning more.
Later, I lost everything in betting.
In the end, I realized I lost everything.
During my service,
I let many criminals, like you, escape.
Do you know why?
Because one day, you may end up
being useful to me.
I am aware that you people
are not that great at what you do.
But I read your case files.
At that point, you didn't seem like
small-timers either.
- Sir?
- Give the phone to the boy.
Okay, Sir.
Hey! Your father wants to talk to you.
Here you go!
- That's awesome!
- It's a fluke.
Hello!
- Jeeva!
- Hey!
Dad?
Jeeva, this is Mom speaking.
I hope nothing's wrong and you're safe.
Nothing to worry, Mom, I'm safe.
But they have chained
my wheelchair to a pillar.
This place looks like a big factory.
But I don't know the location.
Right now, with me,
there are only two uncles.
Jeeva, did anyone out there hit you?
No, Dad, no one hit me.
Hello, Dad?
- Uncle!
- What is it?
The call got disconnected.
Here you go.
You dropped the catch.
Hey, shut up!
Until you people follow my orders...
Jeeva will be safe.
If you guys try to pull something smart...
he won't be alive.
I want money!
I want a lot of money!
I want enough wealth to last me
until I've had my fill of life.
It takes people like you to plan a scam
so carefully and pull it off flawlessly.
And I am certain about it.
Sir, we're not such people.
You have the wrong perspective about us.
Sir, from what you're asking...
I think you believe
we're holding crores somewhere.
How could we give you something
we don't have?
Then, forget about Jeeva.
Sir, we'll do whatever you ask of us.
But one condition.
If we deliver what you demand...
...you must release Jeeva.
He's holding Jeeva hostage
and asking us to make money for him.
And you've given him your word.
How could you agree to it?
What else to do?
It's not like he'll let us go scot-free.
I thought we'd outsmarted Kalyana Sundaram
for 7 years and gone into hiding.
In one second, he broke my bubble.
We did not cheat him
but got cheated by him.
He's not an ordinary man
like you peg him to be.
You don't get it.
He's asking us to get him crores.
- That means we have to steal again.
- We don't have another choice.
If that gets us back, Jeeva,
I'm ready to steal.
For God's sake, don't do anything.
Citing my son as an excuse,
I sinned a lot.
If he's in this situation,
it's our bad karma.
We keep piling on sins...
Forget about it.
Let's find another way to save Jeeva.
I spoke to him after thinking it through.
We don't have another choice.
Did you ever think about this?
We are all escaped criminals.
How do you expect us
to go unnoticed by the people?
Did you think it through?
We were in hiding for our previous crimes.
If we commit another crime
and get caught...
...they'll tear us apart.
But I have a solution.
We must do it.
We must do something
without getting caught.
If you have anything good,
then share it, damn it.
I don't know, either.
I'm thinking as well.
Please give me some time.
Time?
Take your time.
You have made us wait for 7 years
in the hope of getting our money back.
We'll keep waiting!
While you guys are waiting,
shall I make some tea?
Do you have faith that he'll save Jeeva?
I don't have faith in him.
I have a feeling
that he'll get us caught again.
Stay cautious!
This time we should not get caught.
It should be him.
Do you understand?
You overheard us
and are stepping out casually.
Get lost!
I'm sure you're going to
tell him everything.
Will you? Bloody hag!
She's become a nuisance.
The printer broke down at the office.
We won't get caught using this technique.
In Nigeria, they installed
a fake toll booth and swindled crores.
Nigeria is far-fetched.
You can find many similar cases in India.
How could anyone pull off such a big scam?
It may sound like a big scam.
Think about it.
Imagine someone installs a toll booth
on a road you take regularly
and asks for your money.
Are you going to ask them for proof?
You'd eventually pay the toll and move on.
Because people don't have the time
to question anyone.
That's how these scams are successful.
So, when are you getting caught?
- Hello! We're running the toll legally.
- Legal how?
Within a 60-kilometer radius of Chennai,
there shouldn't be a single toll plaza.
But in Chennai, there are 6 toll booths.
And two toll booths belong to your father.
If the Nigerian scamster is looting
by installing a fake toll booth...
...you're joining hands with the
department and scamming people.
- That's the difference!
- Don't act too smart. Get lost!
You're the inside man.
And I'll handle it outside.
I have an idea
that won't get us caught right away.
Say it!
Is it a bank, an ATM,
a casino, or a jewelry shop?
Where are we breaking in?
You mentioned what we would call a heist.
If we do it, we'll be caught in a day
and locked up in prison.
But we're not going to...
...pull of a heist but a scam!
Scam uh?
Good!
Madam has approved!
That means we're up for sacrifice.
This is Mangalapuram.
There used to be a toll booth
near this ring road.
Three years ago, a person filed a case
and temporarily shut down the toll gate.
The toll gate that was shut down
back then, we're going to reinstate it...
and swindle crores from the people.
Fake toll? That's a fantastic plan!
But it sounds like
a huge scam to pull off.
It's a small scam.
Sir, there's an unwritten rule
for every scam.
We cannot continue a scam for long.
If we continue to do it,
we'll get caught.
In China, a man kidnapped
a billionaire gangster's son
and demanded two crores in ransom.
In a few days, two crores got spent.
Again, he carried out another kidnapping.
But this time, not the son
but the billionaire himself.
Do you know why?
To learn how to become rich.
And the billionaire
narrated a story with a smile.
"Create your Own brand."
If you see, the current CEOs
once launched a new product in the market
and became successful.
Today, that gangster is the
top billionaire in that country.
Sir, the toll gate
will fetch us mere crores.
But as you demanded,
you need money until your last breath
For that,
I have an interesting idea, Sir.
FUTURE OF ELECTRICITY
HYDRO GENERATOR SOLUTIONS
Hi, Sir, this is Rohit.
RIT Gold Medalist
in Electrical Engineering.
Electricity has become crucial
in people's lives.
What do people do
during a power shutdown?
They use a generator.
The petrol that runs the generator
is 70 rupees per liter.
However, water is enough
to use the Hydro-Generator.
If you see, this Hydro-Generator
will be the future electricity.
Once, if we launch
this Hydro-Generator in the market,
we could bring huge changes
to the Indian economy.
A part of the money we make from the toll,
we're going to invest in this project.
If you sign a contract with him
and transfer the patent under your name,
all the billionaires will come
looking for you to do business.
"Old Korean Family," you say?
The idea sounds good.
Who is the Director?
It's him.
Oh!
- Who is the Hero?
- That's him too.
- Are you going to do both?
- Yes!
He writes lyrics too.
You see, in the future,
you mentioned you may sing as well.
So, I said it.
You'll don all the roles.
And won't give others an opportunity.
Fine, let's do it!
For the city to believe us,
we must publish the toll gate article
in the newspaper.
I know a reporter who can help us.
Drive! Let's follow him.
Selvam, please deliver a pizza to home.
The Police are checking.
I've already printed the receipt.
You pay the fine
and take your vehicle.
Where are you from?
And where are you headed?
Show me your license!
Sir, show me your license!
Twinkle, twinkle, little star.
Sir, think it's an Anglo Indian family.
Looks like it's a serious matter.
Shall I let them go?
Let them go!
You may leave!
Flat No.6, Arnaa. Is it pizza, right?
- Yes!
- Here, please keep the change.
Okay, the pizza is ready.
- Sir, pizza.
- I'll get your money.
Thank you.
Let's go in!
He passed out!
- Hello?
- Madam, there's an emergency.
It's food poisoning.
- Could you please send an ambulance?
- Okay, Sir, please give me the address.
This is the mock-up
of the article to publish.
TOLL IN MANGALAPURAM AGAIN?
There's a problem.
- Problem?
- What happened?
- It's a server connection mail.
It'll get delivered
only when he's in the office.
Let's drop the plan.
Let's not risk it.
Get out of there.
Get out of there. We'll leave!
What do we do now?
Let's not risk it.
Get out of there.
Mom, I'm discussing.
What do we do?
- Quickly, pack it up.
- Where are we going?
Hey, Saravana,
where are you going in Arnaa's car?
Mom, I'll explain it later.
Hey, Jacky, please listen closely.
Go upstairs and make sure
he doesn't wake up.
I can't do it. Get lost!
Hey, Jacky, please listen.
You must go!
Hey! I already told you.
That I won't go upstairs,
yet you're asking me to.
- I can't go!
- Hey, Jacky, please listen.
Damn you, man. I can't do it.
Brother, this is your sister speaking.
For God's sake, go upstairs.
Please don't refuse.
Bloody, cunning girl.
If I see you, I'll fry you, damn it!
Bloody, brother! Listen to
what he's saying and go upstairs.
Bloody?
Get lost, you crazy girl.
I can't do it.
Jacky, I'll handle it here.
You go upstairs!
Once again, you trapped me.
You never consider me as your child.
You keep sacrificing me
at every given chance.
- Hey, stop talking and go upstairs.
- Hey, hold on, I'm going.
Sir! Arnaa, Sir, ordered a pizza.
Arnaa, Sir, just went home.
Is it so?
Hello? Hello, Arnaa, Sir?
Can you hear me? Can you?
Sir, could you please call Arnaa, Sir?
I think the network is poor.
I'm not able to hear him.
Hello, Sir?
Come to the parking lot right away.
- Sir?
- Don't ask me anything.
- Come right away.
- I'm coming, sir.
- Hello?
- Sir, I'm at the parking lot.
Do you see the flat
and the black-colored gate?
- Flat? I'm at the office parking lot.
- Pizza delivery, right?
Sir, I'm Daily News Admin, Guna, speaking.
I thought you were the pizza delivery guy.
Sorry, Guna!
Pizza delivery is here at the office.
I'll send him to your house.
Sir, placed the order
at the wrong address.
He asked you to come home.
It's done.
The mail has been sent.
Super! Get here quickly.
Hey, Arnaa is gaining consciousness.
- Is he up?
- You handle it.
We'll be there in 10 minutes.
- What do I do?
- Hey, Jacky, please do something!
This is why I didn't want to come here.
Brother, please manage the situation.
When I see you next,
I'm going to thrash you royally.
Stop speaking nonsense
and do something to him.
Cork ball!
How did you manage it?
All of you planned against me...
and turned me into a murderer.
Super!
Oh, God!
Uncle, you're out!
I hope you won't tell anyone
about me getting out.
I won't tell anyone, Uncle.
Shall we play?
I have invited Dhoni.
He'll arrive in an hour.
We'll get together
on the terrace and play.
Is Dhoni coming to play as well?
Yay! Jolly!
Super! I'm going to the terrace.
Brat!
Hey, I think the ambulance has arrived.
I'm alone inside the flat.
What do I do now?
It'll take me 5 minutes to reach.
What do we do now?
Son, I'll handle it!
Mom, you have a stent in your heart,
and you're performing stunts.
What happened?
The vehicle shut down.
It's not starting.
We're heading to pick up
an emergency patient.
His house is at the corner.
Please move your vehicle.
I'm telling you
that I can't start the vehicle.
Reverse and take the entry
on the other side of the road.
Why would you torture us?
- Are you Arnaa from Flat No. 6?
- Yes!
You called for an ambulance
because you got food poisoning.
Check it out.
The toll news is out in the papers.
"A toll booth in Mangalapuram again?"
- She is not recognizable.
- Isn't she?
Perfect!
TOLL IN MANGALAPURAM AGAIN?
We need to perform
a major surgery immediately.
Your health condition is very bad.
This is a critical surgery.
It's impossible to perform.
But we have no choice
but to perform the surgery.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't get you.
Can you do it...
or not?
They must've shut down
the power by mistake.
By the time you get home,
the power will be back on.
Right away, go to this woman
Lakshmi's house
- and switch on the power.
- Okay, sir.
She has an infant
and is struggling without electricity.
Sir, there has been a mistake
in the billing. I'm sorry, sir.
It's common to make mistakes at work.
But you must rectify them.
You're saying the counter is closed?
Go ahead and pay it online.
Call us afterward,
and we'll reconnect your service.
I'm a retired CE.
What does it matter?
That doesn't mean I'll restore
the connection right away.
What kind of progress did you achieve
during your period?
Do you know that there are 16,000
connections under my section?
Ideally, there should be
150 to 200 staff members here.
But only eight employees
are working at this office.
Yet you're demanding
that one employee be sent to your house.
Do whatever you want.
I'll handle it.
The retired CE was arrogant
when he was in power.
Cut off his power for two days.
Okay, sir.
A toll plaza is being set up
in Mangalapuram once again.
Toll? Are they reopening it?
Saravana--
Hey, Saravana! Is that you?
Hey, keep your voice down.
I really thought an old man
was sitting opposite me.
Forget about it.
How are you? What are you up to?
I'm just existing, dude.
Dude, after you left, I invested
in the business and kept it going.
It seemed like I was making money.
Later, I lost it all.
In life, we may win
through shortcuts quickly.
But it does not last.
It lasts only
if you're honest and hard-working.
It's something I learned the hard way.
In life, we have made many mistakes
without thinking twice.
Forget about it.
Do you know something?
Aishu and her family left town
after the mess you created.
They settled down in the USA.
Are you aware of it?
I heard about it.
We'll fix everything.
Okay, Satha!
I'm going to commit another big scam.
I need your help.
What? Once again, you want my help?
- Hey!
- Calm down.
I'm still recovering
from the previous scam.
Do you know something?
Even the kids in my area have
started mocking me, "Quick, Satha."
I have reformed
and am trying to live an honest life.
- Spare me! I'm leaving.
- Satha!
Hey!
Two teas.
Put it under my tab.
No more credit.
- Oh, is it?
- Of course!
- Hey, Satha, please.
- Dude, I can't do it.
- Is this how you see us?
- Sir?
Please don't keep him company.
He'll lure you
to invest in Quick Money and stuff.
Don't trust him!
He's one of the reasons
many have left this town.
Did you hear him?
- Hey, Sakthi, come here.
- Yes, brother?
Here, there are 12 EB cards
and money to pay the bill.
Pay the bill at the EB office.
And demand a printed bill.
If they say the printer is not working
and if you bring me
a paper that says "paid."
- I'll tear you like paper.
- I understood.
You keep repeating this every month.
I know how to pay the bill.
Not just every month.
I'll tell you every day.
Only the victim knows how hard it hit.
Go!
It all started here.
You're right!
The town is convinced now.
Next, we must convince the MLA.
Why are you staring at me?
It's not like I am MLA's wife.
I can't come with you.
Not a chance!
Jacky, one day when you were
down with a cold and fever...
didn't I nurse you back to health?
If something were to happen to me,
the people who are the reason for it
are none but
my biological mother!
I hope everyone heard it.
- What's your name?
- Gangadharan, Sir.
You look like a senior citizen.
I was afraid you'd mess up my hair.
But you're quite an artist.
You inform the others
that I no longer want them.
From now on,
only you should do my hair.
Sir, our company has introduced
a new product.
It's an eye mask. It's enough
if you wear it for 5 minutes.
You'd feel refreshed all day.
- Is it?
- Yes, Sir.
Do it!
Give me 2 minutes. I'll be back.
Thank you.
I'm going to put an eye mask on him.
Inform MLA Senthil that
he'll be getting a call from the Minister.
- Hey, the cheapo MLA is coming.
- Please, welcome.
Have some tea.
Seems like you convinced the CM.
Deputy CM is known to us.
And we used it to our advantage.
Rapta's CEO, Kamala Keerthivasan,
is currently on a video call.
She wants to talk to you for 2 minutes.
Madam, he's here.
Vardharajan, Sir! Okay, Sir.
If you come to Delhi,
you must visit our house.
Please don't forget. Okay, okay.
Hi, Senthil Ji.
- Vanakkam.
- One second.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Water, please.
Thank you.
Senthil Ji, I spoke with Minister
Vardharajan regarding the toll booth.
He'll be calling you right now.
Sir, please set your phone aside.
You can't use your phone
while wearing the eye mask.
Oh, I can't use the phone, right?
One minute.
But I could play a song for 5 minutes.
The plan is messed up.
The Minister played a song on his phone.
It's over!
- What are you saying?
- It's over!
- Plan drop! Plan drop!
- What do we do now?
We can't do anything.
Don't panic.
We'll find a way out.
Let's not risk it and leave.
That's safe for us.
I didn't get a call yet.
Hey, I think the video is freezing.
- It's not working.
- Oh, no!
It's nothing, Sir.
It must be a patchy network.
- That's it. Nothing else.
- Oh, sorry.
She's trying to say something.
But I cannot hear her.
Sir, give me 2 minutes.
Tell me what phone he is using.
- iPhone 6S.
- iPhone... 6S.
Wait a minute.
You can't dial when a song is on.
But there's an option to receive the call.
We can forward the call.
Saravana, even if a song is playing
on iPhone 6S,
you can use another app
in the background.
Go to settings, put your number,
and forward the call.
Call forwarding activated.
Somehow, make MLA Senthil
call the Minister.
- Do you hear me?
- Tell me, Madam.
Sir, Madam, is back online.
Senthil Ji, Minister Vardharajan
has been trying to reach you for a while.
Immediately, please call him.
Vannakam, Sir.
What's happening?
Why am I not able to reach you?
Sir, I think there's an issue
with the network.
Listen, she is the CEO of Rapta Group.
Kamala Keerthivasan. She's a big shot.
Also, she's related to influential people.
Sort out the toll matter for her.
Sure, Sir.
Now that you've said I'll sort it out.
If possible,
you inaugurate the toll as well.
The CM has personally asked
that you be considered for the job.
Sure, Sir. I'll sort it out.
He spoke to me. Don't worry.
I'll take care, Ma'am.
Super, Senthil Ji.
If you're in Delhi, please visit our home.
- Please don't forget.
- I will surely visit.
- Okay.
- Sure, I'll come.
Bye!
Phew!
If you encounter any problems
regarding the toll, reach out to me.
- He has spoken.
- Sir!
Sir, she invited you to Delhi.
Generally, she does not invite everyone.
You're eligible
to become a Central Minister.
I understand.
Bloody moron,
how did you even become an MLA?
- People of Tamil Nadu are--
- Did you say something?
I was praying!
I was praying, Sir.
- Oh, you were praying. Okay.
- Yes!
- Vanakkam!
- Okay, sir.
Hey, this was fantastic.
You look refreshed, Sir.
- What's next? Okay.
- Let me clean up, Sir.
I'm going to rip you both apart,
shredding you.
Son, don't do it!
Jacky!
Any child is a good child at birth.
Whether the child turns out good or evil
depends on how the mother raises them.
- Hey!
- Please don't do it.
Please spare me, Son.
Latest news!
The new movie "Old Korean Boy,"
directed by Kumar, is releasing on Pongal.
Vanakkam, my name is Kumar.
I'm the director of Old Korean Boy,
and it's my dream project.
I got Hero Sir's dates at the right time.
I'm very happy.
- It has come out well.
- Jacky, eat before it gets cold.
- Please eat.
- I need the audience's support.
I'm talking to you--
Hey, why did you?
What happened?
I wrote this script with you in mind.
I can't easily replace you.
No matter how many years it takes,
I'll wait for you.
Sorry, Jacky.
It's all...
...my fault!
As a mother, I should've stopped you
from making these mistakes.
But you did warn me.
And I didn't listen to you.
I can't believe...
I destroyed my son's life.
Only now do I realize it.
When I think about it...
my heart feels heavy.
My son...
I made a mistake.
I made a grave mistake.
I destroyed my son's life.
I'm not a good mother.
Is there dosa flour left?
I'm hungry.
Please make me a dosa.
It's okay, Mom, we'll overcome this.
I get it.
How are you going to
handle the Police station?
A slight suspicion is enough
for them to lock us up.
Hey, why are you people always fighting?
Sir, it's my own house.
He's beating me
whenever I go near the house.
Sir, there's an ongoing case in court.
If he comes near the house
before the verdict, I will beat him.
Sir, you're well aware of the situation.
If it's been past 10 years,
that house will belong to him.
How do you expect me to sit idle?
Sir, I'm the victim here.
Not just him, even his father
comes near the house, I'll beat him.
Hey, what nonsense is this?
Look, he's being violent
right in front of you.
Sir, then ask him to pay me
the 5 lakhs he took from me.
Hey, it's your own house, right?
Why don't you pay him 5 lakhs and end it?
Why would I pay him the money
I never took from him?
I will proceed legally.
Until then, the house is mine.
Sir, my name is Meikannan.
- Okay.
- I'm a senior citizen.
I'm here to file a complaint.
Would it be possible to meet
the inspector at this station?
Oh, you'd only meet the inspector, is it?
Why wouldn't you file a complaint with me?
Oh, no, you misunderstood, Sir.
In Mangalapuram,
a major scam is about to be carried out.
They're going to swindle crores.
So, I wanted to meet the inspector
and file a complaint.
Please wait!
- What scam?
- One minute.
Take a look at this.
There's news about reopening the
toll booth on the Mangalapuram ring road.
As per the rules,
there shouldn't be a toll within
a 60-kilometer radius of Chennai city.
But the Rapta group has acquired
permission to reopen the toll.
Through this toll...
they're going to swindle crores
from the people.
So,
I want to file a complaint against them.
Oh, oh!
Complaint against the Rapta group?
I won't be surprised if you
file a complaint against everyone.
Hey, fool!
Toll doesn't come under State control.
I reckon he's here
to file a controversial complaint.
I want to file a complaint
against the Minister.
What's he saying?
Minister?
Sir, I'm not sure who he is.
There's someone here
to file a complaint against the toll.
Fine, pretend to file a CSR
and send him away.
More will follow to file a complaint.
Please handle it.
Constable, if anyone files
a complaint against toll, don't file it.
- Okay?
- Okay, Sir.
Sir, Rapta Company CEO,
Kamala Keerthivasan is on a video call.
Please talk to her.
- Sure!
- Hi, Sir.
This is Kamala Keerthivasan here.
- How are you, Sir?
- Hi, Ma'am, I'm doing well.
I'm at Mount Everest
for an official meeting.
Oh, is it?
Mount Everest?
You gasp for breath
just by climbing stairs.
She's lying scaling than Everest.
Sir, did MLA Senthil call you
regarding the toll booth?
It's regarding the toll, right?
I'll sort it out.
Okay, Sir. Thank you.
Thank you so much, Sir.
- Thank you.
- Please visit us when you're in Delhi.
- Don't forget.
- Okay.
- I'll visit for sure.
- Madam!
Hey, you never stepped out
of this district.
Don't get us caught by blabbering.
Hang up!
She thanked you, Sir.
Hey, here you go.
Uncle, I can't reach it.
Please help me pick up the food.
You need help?
Fine, I'm coming.
Take it.
Hold it!
You're good at catching things.
Now catch!
It's down here. Catch it.
Catch it!
Hey, you caught it!
Fine, take it.
It's for you to take it.
Uncle, please let it go.
Eat!
I served dinner at the dining table.
Please have it.
Do you really love Jeeva?
Are you truly trying to save Jeeva?
I reckon you'd never trust me.
That's not what I meant.
You're well aware...
that I grew up in an orphanage
since my childhood.
I wanted the usual life
where I fall in love, get married,
have a child,
and live happily with my family.
This is a simple wish.
However,
I made a big mistake in my life.
I trusted the wrong person
and got married to him.
After that, I couldn't trust anyone.
Please don't take me the wrong way.
I don't know
what your impression of me is.
I truly see Jeeva as my own son.
When I said I'm Jeeva's father,
I wasn't saying it for the sake of it.
I meant every word of it.
- Ching Ch Ching
- Make it explode!
-Ching Ch Ching
- Strike fear!
- Run them out!
-Ching Ch Ching
- Intimidate them!
- 80 rupees.
- I'm a local.
I'm the worst local.
I'll chew and spit blade on your face.
To hell with local. Get lost.
VIP? Show me your face.
The camera is being monitored
by the Central Government.
It's election season.
Shall I upload it to TikTok?
- I'm from Press, Sir.
- So? Take out your purse.
The printer is not working.
I'll give you a written receipt.
Day 1 collection: 13,13,000 rupees.
Sir, I'm a lawyer.
I'm asking for the toll fee, not yours.
- I'm a Doctor.
- That doesn't mean I can let you slide.
You guys charge exorbitant fees.
Day 10: 22,00,000 rupees.
90 rupees sounds too expensive, Sir.
If 90 rupees seems expensive,
you don't deserve to drive a car.
He's a Hero, sir.
The one word I don't like in Tamil
is Hero.
But I like the comedian.
Saravana, I was hoping to become a
Hero and enjoy the box office collection.
But you made me sit in a box
and collect money.
The printer is not working.
Here's your receipt.
Toll collection!
Ready!
Welcome to the press and media.
I'm Kalyana Sundaram.
Retired Inspector of Police, Mangalapuram.
After five years of research,
I'm very happy to announce
we have succeeded in creating a
future electricity generation option.
It's called Hydro-Generator.
- Hey, it's Pulp-cane!
- Hey, it's Kalyana Sundaram.
If you're asking
what's special about our generator,
in a normal generator,
you must fuel it with petrol or diesel.
But in our generator,
we don't need that fuel.
Water is enough to power it.
Thanks.
Thank you.
How much are you going to invest in it?
Okay, I'll think about it.
20 crores.
Hello, 30 crores, you say?
40 crores!
Is 50 crores your offer?
Welcome, Saravana!
As you said,
I received a lot of calls.
I finished the final deal
with a Delhi client.
50 crores!
He's going to pay me
an advance of 1 crore.
Fantastic, Sir.
Sir, we collected around 10 crores
through the toll booth.
Sir, we did whatever you asked of us.
If you release Jeeva...
we'll go away somewhere far.
First of all, I never said
I'd let you guys off the hook.
Sir, first, you agreed to let us go.
Now you're going back on your word.
I was going to let you leave.
What if someday you guys return
and con me again?
We won't do anything stupid like that.
If we finish whatever you asked us to do
you agreed to let us leave.
I only agreed to release Jeeva.
I never agreed to release you all.
Sir, harm me as you may like.
But please spare them and release Jeeva.
Sir.
May I speak to Jeeva one last time?
- Yes, Sir.
- Pass the phone to the boy.
Okay, Sir.
Your father wishes to talk to you
for one last time.
Here you go!
Jeeva, this is Dad speaking.
Tell me, Dad.
I made a lot of mistakes in life.
Also, I encouraged you to make mistakes.
Hereafter in life,
you must not harm or hurt anyone.
Okay, Dad.
Jeeva, how many men are around you?
It's the same two uncles, Dad.
But they're a bit far from me.
- Do you remember my number?
- Yes, Dad!
Then stand up and run!
Send your location to my number
and keep running.
- I'll be there soon!
- Okay, Dad!
When will I be able to participate
in a running race?
Next year, Son.
Yay! Jolly!
- Brother, he's running away.
- Hey, catch him!
Hey, stop right there!
Hey, watch out, kid.
Listen, this school won't work out.
We need a high recommendation.
Looks like a rich people's school.
Let's leave.
I wish to put Jeeva in a school like this.
Mom, ask him to
find a way to get admission.
- Ouch!
- Hey, can't you watch out?
- You'll stop only when you get hurt.
- Get up!
Admissions are closed, Sir.
It's hard to find a seat here.
Please look for another school.
Dad, my leg is not responding.
Jeeva!
Sir, why didn't you mention
that your son is physically challenged?
The admission is still discreetly open.
Refer to my name and fill out
the form in the admissions office.
Dad, I'm not lying.
The leg is not responding.
There's an option.
We'll say Jeeva is physically challenged
and, get an admission.
Two years later,
we'll tell them he recovered.
Jeeva, what Dad did today
was morally wrong.
I'm sorry.
No matter what happens in your life...
you must not make the mistakes I did.
I've made plenty of mistakes on purpose,
without considering the impact.
But the first time I felt guilty was
when I made a small boy
like Jeeva commit a mistake.
I'm the reason
why Jeeva is in this situation.
I'm the cause of all the problems.
I will fix it!
Kalyana Sundaram, who knew us well,
missed out on one thing.
He did not know that Jeeva could walk.
There's a reason why Jeeva
never got off the wheelchair.
It's because he made a promise to me.
Will you promise me one thing?
Except when you're in the house
wherever you go or until I say so
you must not get off the wheelchair.
Promise?
Promise!
When we spoke with Jeeva, he said
that only his wheelchair has been chained.
They have chained my wheelchair
to a pillar, Mom.
But he's not chained.
- Also, he mentioned a factory.
- It looks like a factory.
Hey, don't run!
Hey, Saravana, open the door.
I'm going to commit another big scam.
I need your help.
Jeeva, the location is
20 minutes from here.
Jeeva, are you safe?
I'm safe and running, Dad.
Sir!
Do it now!
My mother was saying...
only after I get married to you,
my life will be bright and shinning.
Mummy?
Hey!
Where are you?
You're looking in the wrong place.
I'm here, damn it, not there.
Come and get me!
Bloody little devil!
Hey, open the door!
On that night,
when Kalyana Sundaram called Jeeva...
the phone displayed Padi Siva.
So, he must be held captive near Padi.
Suppose he's not in Padi?
- Hello?
- Hello!
- Sir, it's Saravana speaking.
- Saravana!
- Is it really you?
- Yes, Sir.
Where were you all these years?
I trusted you so much.
At least you could've told me.
Fine, tell me now.
Or else my head will explode.
Tell me what exactly happened.
Saravana, the entire city of Chennai
will be blacked out.
To restart the electricity,
it'll take another 20 minutes.
Okay, enjoy!
- Enjoy yourself.
- Thank you, Darling.
Hey, you're always welcome.
Bye!
Please ask him to drive slowly.
Hey, won't you keep the car ready to go?
- Hey, drive carefully.
- Hey, don't fall on me.
Hey, drive slowly.
I caught you!
Get lost!
Mom, ask him to drive more slowly.
On, on! On, on, on!
Jeeva!
Oh, God!
- Come here.
- Jeeva!
Dad!
Hey!
I'm sorry, Son.
From now on, I won't be late.
Okay!
Hello, Rohit, where are you?
- Yes, Kalyan, Sir.
- The machine is not working
But the water is running.
What do I do?
It's simple.
There's a motor switch next to it.
Switch it off.
- Automatically, the water will stop.
- What?
Did you say to switch off
the motor switch to stop the water?
Hey, the machine is not working.
What do I do now?
When the tank overflows,
switching off the motor is the solution.
Hello, Sir, are you still connected?
Hey, I think he froze for the second time.
Clearly explain it to him.
Hello, Sir, this is Saravanan speaking.
What happened?
Are you confused?
Is your head spinning?
The toll scam is not
a quick get-in-and-out scam.
So, we'll have ample time
to find a way to save Jeeva.
Moreover, to divert Kalyana Sundaram
we would need another dummy idea.
As per our plan,
we need an electrical engineer.
Meet him.
Could you please cover for me?
I'll be back soon.
Will Kalyana Sundaram believe him?
What's his weakness?
I started small-time betting.
I won!
Gambling!
Quick Money and gambling are the same.
Money earned through quick methods
always poses danger.
It's easy to convince them.
You wait and watch.
This is a coffee tray, this is the motor,
heater, and this is the meter.
Heater?
It's junk art.
I'll give a fantastic presentation.
Hey, Baldie!
- Do you know who Kalyana Sundaram is?
- He did mention.
He's a marriage broker, right?
Dude, do you ever speak the truth?
Ji, shall I paint the heater pink?
Pink?
White is good enough.
We could bring major changes
in the Indian economy, sir.
You see, this wire travels all the way
and is connected to his machine.
That's why the three lights are on.
He's the best scientist, Sir.
The water is enough to power it.
My Boss is interested in your project.
- Five crores.
- We can push it till 20 crores.
- 40 crores.
- 50 crores.
Saravana, you may have cheated me on this.
Don't forget you committed a huge scam.
You can't easily escape from it.
This time you're messing with
the Central Government.
They will be on to you wherever you go.
Guys, for the third time, I got Joker.
We won!
Explain the same to the potty mouth.
Sir, let me explain something.
Actually, we were going to
spare you and leave.
But only after we arrived
we learnt something about you.
In my service, I let many criminals,
like you, escape.
Only after hearing that did we
have a strong suspicion of you.
Later at reporter Arnaa's place,
I found a file named Sabari.
That file contained evidence
of how my friend Sabari died.
Only after I arrived here
did I learn that you killed Sabari.
During an illegal business deal,
he was shot dead in a crossfire
between two gangs.
Bye, dude!
For safety, I always save a copy
of whatever I record.
Did you see?
Thank your stars I was here.
If it were someone else,
all of you would've been on Flash news.
This is Sabari's daughter.
Grandpa!
I'm telling the truth.
It's with Sabari.
Whenever I ask him about the money
he brings up Sabari.
- What do we do, Sir?
- Let them escape.
That means our money
is with Kalyana Sundaram.
I alone would've been trouble for him.
Imagine if we all come together.
Shall we show him our prowess?
We never wanted to return to Manglapuram.
But you brought us here.
But in a way, you did a good thing.
After learning that you're the reason
why our lives were ruined...
how could we let you go unscathed?
Breaking news!
Retired Inspector Kalyana Sundaram,
installed a fake toll booth in Magalapuram
and swindled crores.
We need to establish a paper trail
connecting Kalyana Sundaram
to the toll booth scam.
We're going to record everything
using this hidden cam.
Fake toll? It's a fantastic plan!
Oh, so Kalyana Sundaram is a fraud too.
Is Kalyana Sundaram a fraud too?
Seems like he's a fraud.
I can't believe I trusted him.
So, the Pulp-cane Kalyana Sundaram
is a fraud too.
In addition,
we have information linking him
to a new scam involving hydro-generators.
Based on this information,
the police arrested him.
I hear noise in the background.
I think they've arrived!
As you mentioned,
the Central Government
has arrived.
Hey, Wedding-Sundaram!
If we were the talk of the town,
you're the talk of the country.
You always quote one thing.
"Being cheated is a greater sin
than cheating."
Now, let me share a quote.
"It's wrong to cheat.
It's just as wrong to get cheated."
You guys made a mistake.
I won't let you off the hook.
Does this mean...
we have reformed?
Bad mother.
Don't deceive, deceive no one
Brother!
But do not be deceived
By trusting!
Don't deceive, deceive no one
Brother!
But do not be deceived
Filled with lies of every hue
He crafted this earthen realm
Sowing countless little hopes
He let us run, only to block our way
And the tale ended there
I sincerely apologize
for all the trouble I caused you.
I realized my mistake very late.
I hope you can forgive me.
- Sorry.
- Saravanan.
- Mithra.
- Jacky and Janaki.
Brother!
Hey, Satha!
He thinks he is Paul Walker. Get lost!
Filled with lies of every hue
He crafted this earthen realm
Sowing countless little hopes
He let us run, only to block our way
And the tale ended there
- Dude, I have some good news.
- Tell me.
Sudha Illam is now Satha Illam.
Hey, I'm trusting you
and taking a loan against this house.
If I miss even one EMI,
they'll come after me.
- Bear this in mind.
- Hey, I won't miss it.
I'll make the payments on time.
Okay, bye.
-Bye.
- Take care. See you.
Let unrest rise in every heart
Nurture it, and it becomes a storm
One bite of that rock-solid roti
Grandpa's dentures turned red quickly
Let the whole city rise and applaud
Tighten the cage
Watch me tear it apart
Even Harry Potter gets knocked out
In one shot
If needed
I unleash Power Rangers Ninja Storm
Brother, sir likes your acting.
He'll recommend you for his next
project too. What's your name?
King! King! King!
Out here, I'm the king
I'm about to sound the call
King! King! King!
Rambo!
Rambo Selvaraj!
I'm about to sound the call
Did you book tickets for Bigil?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I forgot about it.
You always forget things!
I don't care what you have to do.
I want to watch Vijay's movie
on the first day, first show.
Alright, I get it.
I'll make the arrangements.
Okay?
- And we're going out for dinner tonight.
- I will be there.
Bye.
- Sir?
- Hello!
I got a message saying today is the last
day to pay my brother's college fees.
Shall I pay the fees?
You wouldn't receive a text
under any circumstances.
I think it was a technical glitch.
Sir, the due date is still 20 days away.
Pay it later. No rush.
Oh, is it?
It's okay, sir. I'll pay it now.
- Student's name?
- Vijay.
- ID number?
- 6537.
Please give it to me.